carhartt.com 2019-09-27

# Carhartt Privacy Policy

**CARHARTT WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Updated: November 29, 2017 

We appreciate the trust you place in Carhartt, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for [www.carhartt.com](https://www.carhartt.com/). The statement does not include the privacy practices for partnered sites. We encourage our users who visit external sites from links within Carhartt.com to read the privacy statements of those sites, as their privacy practices may differ from ours and will govern their using your information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should first contact us via [e-mail](mailto:just_ask_us@carhartt.com) or by calling 1-800-833-3118. If you prefer to write us our postal address is below. 

Carhartt Customer Service   
P.O. Box 600   
Dearborn, MI 48126 

**How We Disclose Personal Data**  
Carhartt will only disclose your Personal Data with your knowledge and as stated in this Privacy Policy or as indicated at the time of collection. This includes disclosures that will enable us to fulfill our obligations to you, and allows us to manage our business operations. We will only share your Personal Data with third parties in certain limited instances, namely with your consent, or as is necessary to complete a transaction or provide a product, service, or feature that you have requested. We may disclose your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy and in the following ways: 

At Carhartt, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect information that allows us to: 

Improve our merchandise selection and customer service 

**Cookies**

We regularly use technologies such as cookies. A "cookie" is a small file stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow us to recognize who you are, when you arrive at our site, by associating an anonymous identification number in the cookie. At no time is your personally identifiable information stored within one of our cookies. 

We have selected an outside company, Omniture by Adobe, to assist us in better understanding how people use our site. Cookies will be placed on your computer to collect non-personal information. The information that is collected through these cookies tells us things like which search engine referred you, how you navigated around our site, what you browsed and purchased and what traffic is driven by banner ads and emails. Carhartt.com does not allow Omniture by Adobe to collect credit card, username or password information. 

Cookies allow us to understand how you clicked to our site and what pages you click on during your visit to our site. Understanding how you shop allows us to improve and personalize your shopping experience and speed your checkout process. We may use technologies such as cookies to provide you with personalized display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of this advertising provided by Carhartt, [click here](https://dtmc.carhartt.com/adinfo/adchoices_fpc.html?cid=2625&cname=Carhartt&cmagic=6412fe&clogo=Carhartt.png). 

Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies. 

We also contract with a third-party advertising partner to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services which may appear on other sites that you visit. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partner, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices. 

**How We Use Email**

When you provide us your email address, we may send you emails related to processing your order or to respond to a request. For example, after you place an order at carhartt.com, you will receive an email confirmation and, in most cases, an email with package tracking information. 

If you decide to participate in our Field Testing Program your email address will be used to send you surveys periodically. 

**Security**

In our efforts to protect your information, Carhartt uses a variety of technical safeguards, such as firewalls, and we physically secure our servers. 

In addition, when you make a purchase, request a catalog, or create an account on our website, your information is transmitted in an encrypted format. 

The Carhartt.com website may contain links to other sites. Carhartt does not control the use of personally identifiable information on these websites. You should review the privacy policies of every website before providing any personal information. Carhartt is not responsible for the conduct or practices of any linked websites. These links are provided solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. 

**Privacy of Children on Our Website**

Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

**Policy Changes**

From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy notice. Before our information practices change, we will post these changes on our website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.

**Questions or Comments?**

For questions, comments or assistance, we invite you to contact us

We hope to answer any questions to your satisfaction, but should you ever want to contact a third party regarding our privacy practices, you can email the Direct Marketing Association's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org. The DMA is the oldest and largest association for consumers and companies with interest in direct marketing. You may also contact the Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202-FTC-HELP (202-382-4357 ) or electronically at https://www.ftc.gov/ro/index.shtml
